<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Tiffany Chieu</title>
    <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Tiffany Chieu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://tchieu.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>imgproc-rs</title>
      <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/imgproc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tchieu.com/projects/imgproc/</guid>
      <description>Repository  Crates.io  Documentation       This image processing library provides a flexible container for storing and manipulating different image formats and channel data types, and supports the following types of image operations:  Color space conversions between sRGB, HSV, CIE XYZ, and CIELAB Brightness, contrast, and saturation adjustments Gamma correction and histogram equalization Linear filtering through convolution Nonlinear filters such as the median, bilateral, and alpha-trimmed mean filters Basic affine transformations Morphological operations   In addition, this library supports multithreading for some transformation functions and most filter functions via rayon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>space-invaders</title>
      <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/space-invaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tchieu.com/projects/space-invaders/</guid>
      <description>Repository       For this project, I implemented a version of the arcade game Space Invaders in Verilog using a Nexys3 Spartan 6 FPGA board. The game consists of:  A player, which can be moved left and right across the bottom of the screen A laser, which can be shot upwards from the player&#39;s laser base A 5x11 grid of invaders that continuously moves left and right across the middle of the screen 3 missiles, which the invaders somewhat randomly shoot down towards the player  Initial game state</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TI-RSLK Path Follower</title>
      <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/rslk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tchieu.com/projects/rslk/</guid>
      <description>The goal of this project was to develop a path-following car based on the TI-RSLK car platform using a series of IR sensors and a PID controller. Code for the path-following system can be found here, and code for the basic Arduino PID controller that was used can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VulcaNet</title>
      <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/vulcanet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tchieu.com/projects/vulcanet/</guid>
      <description>Created by: Tiffany Chieu, Nashir Janmohamed, Justin Lin, and Ariel Young
Awards: Best IoT that Incorporates Multiple Nodes, San Diego Hackathon 2019
Repository  Devpost       The goal of this project is to provide a reliable, low-cost early detection system for wildfires.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
