<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Tiffany C. Chieu</title>
    <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Tiffany C. Chieu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://tchieu.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>imgproc-rs</title>
      <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/imgproc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tchieu.com/projects/imgproc/</guid>
      <description> crates.io Full documentation   I wrote this basic image processing library mainly for the purpose of learning about image processing techniques and learning the Rust programming language. Check out the links above to learn more! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TI-RSLK Path Follower</title>
      <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/rslk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tchieu.com/projects/rslk/</guid>
      <description>ECE 3 Final Project   The goal of this project was to develop a path-following car based on the TI-RSLK car platform using a series of IR sensors and a PID controller. Code for the path-following system can be found here, and code for the basic Arduino PID controller that was used can be found here. The path-following system began with an auto-calibration routine in which the car was placed over a white area, followed by a black area, from which minimum and maximum values were calibrated for each sensor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VulcaNet</title>
      <link>https://tchieu.com/projects/vulcanet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tchieu.com/projects/vulcanet/</guid>
      <description>Created by: Tiffany Chieu, Nashir Janmohamed, Justin Lin, and Ariel Young Awards: Best IoT that Incorporates Multiple Nodes, San Diego Hackathon 2019   The goal of this project is to provide a reliable, low-cost early detection system for wildfires. VulcaNet is an extensible IoT mesh network that aggregates environmental sensor data from various locations within a given area, such as ambient temperature, humidity, barometric pressure, and carbon dioxide air content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
